eforms.com 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy | eForms – Free Fillable Forms

**Updated: July 1, 2016**

We care about your privacy and we make protecting your privacy one of our priorities. This Privacy Policy relates to collecting data, use of data, use of our: software, platform, services, and websites (collectively, “Products”) provided by Electronic Forms, LLC, a Florida Limited Liability Company and/or any of our affiliates (collectively, “eForms”). By using our Products, you consent to our methods and procedures described in this policy as well as our Terms of Use Agreement. In the event that you do not agree with any provision in our privacy policy, please do not continue to use the Products.

**1\. Collection of Personal Information.**

In the event that you decide to purchase our Products, we will collect and store your billing and credit card information. In addition, eForms may collect your personal information including but not limited to your e-mail address, name, physical address and telephone number as well as demographic information. Unless, the customer is a paying customer, eForms reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to delete customer’s information at any time. Information about your computer may be automatically collected by eForms including, but not limited to your: IP address, browser type, domain names visited, access times and referring website addresses. eForms uses this information for operations, quality control and for statistical feedback. If you disclose your personal information through the Products, it may collected by others. You may want to review the privacy statements of any websites you click on from our website. Their information collection and use policy may be different. eForms is not responsible for the privacy statements or any other content, services or products on third-party websites.

**2\. Personal Information.**

Use eForms collects and uses your information in order to operate our websites and provide any Products that you request. In addition, your information may be used by eForms to inform you of other products or services available from eForms and its affiliates in which you might be interested or ask you to participate in research surveys regarding the Products. eForms will not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. However, eForms may contact you on behalf of its business affiliates about a particular product or service. No personal information is transferred to such affiliate without your consent. eForms may share your information with third parties who provide services, such as customer support, or deliveries, but in such cases, the third parties are forbidden to use your information except to facilitate providing the Products you request. eForms tracks page visits of customers in order to be able to deliver our Products, other customized content and advertising within the websites. In addition, other parties who perform data analytics for eForms, such as Google Analytics, may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our Products. eForms makes no representations about any third party data collection mechanisms. eForms only shares browser-level data through third party vendor tracking such as Google Analytics. Users can opt out of these advertising features by visiting Google or resources like the NAI consumer opt-out page. eForms may use email addresses to target users with custom ads through 3rd party advertising platforms. eForms shares customer information with third parties to perform services on our behalf. eForms may disclose personal information if we believe it is required or appropriate, such as to comply with the law, to collect funds owed to us, to protect our users, or in the event of an emergency. Finally, eForms may disclose personal information as part of a business transaction or in the event of bankruptcy or insolvency if such information is considered a business asset. eForms will do its best to inform customers if such an event transpires, however, there may not be a chance to opt out in such a case.

**3\. Cookies.**

eForms may use “cookies” to optimize your experience with our Products. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive, but they may not be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and when you return to our website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can continue to use any Products that you previously customized. You may accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser settings. If you decline cookies, the use of the Products may not be optimized.

**4\. Security.**

You are solely responsible for preventing unauthorized use of your user information including your password. You agree that you are responsible for any activity under your account whether you authorized such activity or not. You agree to immediately notify eForms of any unauthorized use of your account. eForms secures the personally identifiable information you provide on its servers in a controlled and secure environment which is protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. eForms encrypts account information during transmission to other websites using protocols such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL).

**5\. Children Under Eighteen (18) Years of Age.**

Our Products are not intended for use by children under the age of 18, and such use is prohibited by our Terms of Service. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 18. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us immediately.

**6\. Changes and Amendments to this Privacy Policy.**

eForms may amend the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and will post the most recent version on our website.

**7\. Contact Information.**

eForms welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. To [Contact Us](https://eforms.com/contact/) at anytime, feel free to either call **1(855) 779-5770** , [E-Mail](mailto:support@eforms.com), or use our [Online Chat](https://eforms.com/contact/).

For additional information, please review our [Terms of Use](https://eforms.com/terms-of-use/).
